

# NGO VAN TRUNG

+84 94 612 9294 | trung2601.it@gmail.com | github.com/TrungNgoVan

## **ABOUT ME**

I'm Trung, a third-year Mathematics and Computer Science major at VNUHCM - University Of Science. I'm passionate about programming and technology. I have experience working on several real projects. I am particularly interested in becoming a Backend Developer. I have strong self-study and time management skills to help me achieve this goal.

## **EDUCATION**

BSC IN COMPUTER SCIENCE & MATHEMATICS University of Science, VNU-HCM | GPA: 7.8/10 (3.3/4)

## **SKILLS**

# **Programming:**

- Language: Python, JavaScript, C/C++, Go
- Framework: Django, ExpressJS
- Knowledge: OOP, DSA, Database, Network
  Database: MongoDB, MySQL, Redis, MinIO
- Deployment: Docker
- · Project versioning: Git
- API development: Postman

#### Other:

- Communication
- Leadership

## **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- 2023
  - Top 20 GDSC HACKATHON VIETNAM 2023 (Role Backend)
- 2022
  - o Top 238 Shopee Code League.
  - o Top 5 HCMUS Student Competition with ASEAN Information Security
  - Top 10 mentor YOUPRENEUR LAUNCHPAD 2022.
- 2021
  - o Champion "Đi tìm thủ lĩnh HCMUS 2021"
- 2018
  - Silver medal at the Informatics Olympiad in Dak Lak province.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **BACKEND INTERN**

- Approi Ltd. Growth Marketing Agency
- Utilize Django for web application development with expertise in Django Rest Framework
  1 09/2023 Now

#### **BACKEND DEVELOPER**

Google Developer Student Clubs Chapter HCMUS

| 12/2022 - Now

## **MENTOR**

- Mentor 2 startup projects in Youpreneur Launchpad 2022
- Support ideas, technology tools for project implementation

| 5/2022 - 8/2022

#### **TEACHING ASSISTANT**

- Kmin Academy Học viện khoa học máy tính
- Basic Javascript, C++, Typescript classes

| 2/2022 - 8/2023

#### **MEMBER**

- PiMA Projects in Mathematics and Applications
- · Contribute an article about "Dynamic programming" on fanpage

| 9/2021 - 3/2023

# **PROJECTS**

## **Project Student Manager System**

- Use C++, knowledge of OOP and data structure
- Basic CRUD app for managing students' info in universities

## **Project Authentication API**

- Use ExpressJS, MongoDB
- Use JWT authentication for user authentication and authorization.
- Use Bcryptjs for password encoding and decoding

# Blog "Sổ tay của Henry"

- Built with Hugo
- . Blog about my algorithm, technology, experience in the field of programming

## **Morning Basket**

- Role: Backend NodeJS (main)
- Use Javascript, ReactJS, MongoDB
- Use knowledge of authenticate, database, design e-commerce API

## **App chat Django**

- Role: Backend Python (Django) & Frontend (HTML, CSS)
- Use Python Channel, WebSocket, MySQL
- Use knowledge of restAPI, web-socket connection, design real-time application